registryfix.com 2016-03-06

# RegistryFix

|  |  | 

Privacy Policy

RegistryFix.com is committed to protecting your privacy and personal information when you access our website and software. This policy governs how we treat personal information that is collected when you visit or subscribe to services offered at our site.

**Information we collect**

When you make a purchase at our website, the only information we ever collect is your full name, email address, and purchase date. All personal information such as credit card information, zip code and location is collected and stored by our third party payment processor, who maintains a strict privacy policy governing the use of said information.

**How information we collect is used**

We may use information we collect to:

  * To process and validate purchase information. 
  * To notify you of any product upgrades, bugs, or new versions. 
  * To verify that you are a registered customer.
  * We may disclose your information if required to do so by any government or law enforcement official.

**Cookies**

We define a cookie as a small text file of information placed on your hard drive automatically when visiting our site. All cookies used on our site contain no personally identifiable information and are used to make your browsing experience better, or to allow proper tracking of any visitors sent to us by sales partners.

**Security**

Any information collected about you is stored on limited access servers, and we maintain rigorous safeguards to prevent against any unauthorized intrusion to these servers. The only information stored about you is your full name, email address, and purchase date.

**Links**

We may at times provide you with links to other websites which are not under the control of our company. Please be aware that the sites are not governed by this privacy policy, and all may provide different policies at their respective websites.

**Policy Modifications**

We may change this privacy policy at any time without notice to you in order to provide your information with better protection or to reflect our company practices.

**Acceptance of Terms**

By using this website, you are consenting to this privacy policy and acceptance of the information described above.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy or terms described above, please contact us at [business@RegistryFix.com](mailto:business@RegistryFix.com)

|  |   

“Your program found and eliminated 486 problems in my system. After fixing the errors, my computer responded tremendously, and there are no more errors when I start up my PC. Thanks so much!”

\-- Amy Kinneberg

“It is no exaggeration to say that my computer and internet surfing now run about 10 times faster since I used your software. I can't thank you enough for your great program!”

\-- Jim Brown

“Wow!!! Have just completed downloading and using your software, am amazed at results! 606 Faults were found, have only had computer 6 months, so i was not expecting such a high number. Computer is running much much faster now. Thanks again.”

\-- Timothy Sapowitz

“I Just wanted to let ya'll know that your program is GREAT. I have had my computer for less than 6 months and there were 779 problems found. WOW!!!!! Great going and keep it up.”

\-- Matt Jorgunson

 |  |   
---|---|---|---|---|---|---
